Two wins and one loss
二胜一负
Characters, places and events are fictitious
人物、地点和事件均为虚构
Yes, I'm almost home.
是的，我快到家了。
Episode 6
第6集
Today is a crazy day for you.
今天对你来说是疯狂的一天。
Absolutely.
绝对地。
I've been to heaven and hell.
我去过天堂和地狱。
This is a busy company.
这是一家繁忙的公司。
I'm happy to have something to work with.
我很高兴有事情 可以合作。
You are wonderful. There is no hope for you.
你太棒了。你没有希望。
-Who has it? -Hey, I have a client. I have to go.
-谁有？ -嘿，我有一个客户。我得走了。
nobody. Enter.
没有人。进入。
-What? -What are you doing in there?
-什么？ -你在里面做什么？
there is nothing. I rest.
没有什么。我休息。
Why did you come up?
你为什么上来？
Also rest.
也要休息。
Are you too tired to even go to the elevator?
连电梯都累得不行吗？
Yes.
是的。
Did you sell a lot?
你卖了很多吗？
Then shouldn't you feel happy and satisfied?
那你不应该感到高兴 和满足吗？
I've dealt with a lot of people
我和很多人打过交道
They sucked my energy.
他们吸走了我的能量。
The more you sell, the more fatigue you get.
销售越多，疲劳就越多。
You are fine.
你很好。
I need a man's hand, not yours.
我需要一个男人的手，而不是你的。
my God.
我的上帝。
Sweet and delicate touch.
甜美细腻的触感。
Don't do that.
不要那么做。
Someone said my belly was fine and rubbed it.
有人说 我的肚子很好并抚摸它。
seriously.
严重地。
This is why you can't be friends with your daughter.
这就是为什么你不能 和你女儿做朋友。
You can never talk to her about men.
你永远不能和她谈论男人。
I don't want to be your friend either.
我也不想成为你的朋友。
Why this expression?
为什么这副表情？
Do I look tired?
我看起来很累吗？
Why do you look like a zombie?
为什么你看起来像僵尸？
Huajia.
华贾。
Yes.
是的。
What should I do to make my boss like me?
我该怎么做才能让老板喜欢我？
It's time for us to go now.
我们现在该走了。
She is on another level.
她处于另一个层面。
Much taller than mine.
比我的高很多。
But I want to make a lasting impression
但我想给人留下深刻的印象
and get his approval.
并得到他的认可。
Come on, let's go. I don't want to miss this drama.
来吧，我们走吧。 我不想错过这部戏剧。
Can't you just listen to me for a minute?
你就不能听我说一分钟吗​​？
I pat your shoulder.
我拍拍你的肩膀。
I've never had a boss like this in my life
我这辈子从来没有遇到过这样的老板
So I don't know. View.
所以我不知道。观点。
OK let's go.
好的。我们走吧。
cell movement
细胞运动
Now you take care of it.
现在你来照顾它。
It will be your responsibility,
这将是你的责任，
This proposal is made by you.
该提案由您提出。
Jaemin
宰珉
Yunzhu
允珠
He didn't answer.
他没有回答。
call lost
通话丢失
So will you stay here?
那你就留在这里吗？
Yes.
是的。
Aren't you looking for a house?
你不是在找房子吗？
Why do you want to see me?
你为什么想见我？
I want to ask you something.
我想问你一件事。
Didn't you say you would never come back?
你不是说你永远不会回来了吗？
Yes.
是的。
So why…
那么为什么…
Why did you come back?
你为什么回来？
It seems this is what everyone wants to know.
看来这是 每个人都想知道的。
You don't seem to mean that.
你好像不是这个意思。
You act like you're never coming back.
你表现得 就像你永远不会回来一样。
So think of it as a gap year.
因此，将其视为间隔年。
You keep running. take a break.
你不停地跑。休息一下。
Look how things are going in South Korea.
看看韩国的情况如何。
But why me?
但为什么是我？
You even want to kneel down.
你甚至想跪下。
Yes, sincerely.
是的，真诚的。
Most board members are followers of the vice president,
大多数董事会成员 都是副总裁的追随者，
meaning is
意思是
My position was not secure.
我的地位并不稳固。
Let ASG Consultants serve as Communications Manager
让 ASG 顾问 担任传播经理
It will change the horizons of foreign investors .
它将改变外国投资者的视野 。
This will give me the opportunity to reorganize the Board of Governors.
这将使我有机会 重组理事会。
Who Can Object to Replacement of Board Members
谁可以反对更换 董事会成员
Who knows ASG best?
谁最了解 ASG？
So you want to use me for this?
所以你想利用我来做这个？
To solidify your position as CEO?
为了巩固你作为首席执行官的地位？
You want to be sincere.
你想要真诚。
you are right.
你是对的。
You just have to impress me and stay with me.
你只需要给我留下好印象 并留在我身边就可以了。
i want to take a rest
我想休息一下
And the condition is very good.
而且条件很好。
I am disappointed.
我很失望。
I didn't expect such a response.
我没想到会有这样的回应。
What response were you expecting?
你期待什么回应？
Because I want to see you?
因为我想见你？
You are the reason I got into this field.
你是我进入这个领域的原因。
official apology
官方道歉
- Say hello to staff. -excellent.
- 向工作人员问好。 -极好的。
Shiyong announces 2022 selection list
世勇公布2022年选拔名单
Specializes in blindly recruiting experienced workers.
专门盲目招聘 有经验的工人。
Our response was not adequate
我们的反应不够充分
This led to the emergence of recruitment controversies .
导致招聘争议的出现 。
To employees who may have suffered emotional distress as a result of our errors,
对于因我们的错误而可能遭受精神困扰的员工，
We offer our sincerest apologies.
我们致以最诚挚的歉意。
Zero qualification excuse
零资格的借口
I logged on this morning to apologize.
今天早上我登录是为了道歉
Zero qualifications.
零资格。
I read their apology and it was shocking.
我读了他们的道歉 ，这令人震惊。
I am disturbed by the company's spineless attitude.
我 对公司毫无骨气的态度感到不安。
Anyway, sorry, Miss Zero Qualifications.
无论如何，对不起， 零资格小姐。
Next stop, Euljiro 1-ga.
下一站，乙支路1街。
Diligence, harmony, integrity
勤奋、和谐、诚信
listen.
你听。
Regarding this question about employees…
关于员工的这个问题……
The employees were talking about it
员工们纷纷议论纷纷
Because you give them trust.
因为你给予他们信任。
You even publicly apologized today .
今天你甚至公开 道歉。
Was he trying to make things worse?
他是想让事情变得更糟吗？
You are the CCO, right?
你是 CCO，对吗？
It stands for Chief Creative…
它代表首席创意……
Anyway,
反正，
That's not why we gave her the position.
这不是 我们给她职位的原因。
I called her because I couldn't take it anymore.
我给她打电话是因为我再也受不了了。
And it's not just me. Imagine how Mr. Jung.
而且不仅仅是我。 想象一下先生的感受。荣格.
then? Can you explain it to us?
当时？你能给我们解释一下吗？
What makes the situation worse is when companies run low or low on inventory
情况变得更糟的是公司库存不足或不足
Condition.
情况。
Just because management ignores it, doesn't mean the problem goes away.
仅仅因为管理层忽视了它， 并不意味着问题就消失了。
This is a PR mistake.
这是一个公关错误。
Why does management raise this issue?
管理层为何提出这个问题？
PR departments are afraid of management.
公关部门害怕管理层。
How dare he say such a thing?
他怎么敢说出这样的话？
From his standpoint?
从他的立场来看？
They don't want to upset Mr. Jung,
他们不想让先生不高兴。荣格,
Adding fuel to the fire.
火上浇油。
Sigla Gu!
西格拉·古！
The PR office represents the company.
公关办公室代表公司。
Their job is to communicate with employees on behalf of the company.
他们的工作是代表公司与员工沟通。
When did they care so much about their employees' jobs?
他们什么时候这么关心 员工的工作了？
If we admit we made a mistake
如果我们承认自己犯了错误
Will employees misjudge us?
员工会不会误判我们？
affim. That's exactly what I said.
肯定。这正是我所说的。
Better to do nothing.
最好什么也不做。
He is in Korea now, okay?
他现在在韩国，好吗？
We do things differently here.
我们在这里做事不同。
Do I really have to tell him?
我真的必须告诉他吗？
explain. Jung.
说。荣格.
Are you still reading print media?
您还在阅读印刷媒体吗？
Promote your company on traditional channels like this
在这样的传统渠道上推广公司
This is no longer the purpose of public relations.
这不再是 公共关系的目的。
Today, businesses should...
如今，企业应该...
Sigla Gu!
西格拉·古！
How dare you teach him a lesson?
你怎么敢教训他？
I don't want to hear excuses. I'd like to hear your thoughts.
我不想听到借口。 我想听听你的想法。
As CCO, what do you think you did wrong?
作为 CCO，您认为自己做错了什么？
I see.
我明白。
I got you.
我明白你的意思。
But unfortunately,
但不幸的是，
I have to go.
我得走了。
As a communications manager, I carefully evaluate where I went wrong.
作为一名传播经理，我会仔细评估自己错在哪里。
excuse me.
打扰一下。
Sigla Gu.
西格拉·古。
Sir, ignore her. Jung.
先生，别理她。荣格.
God, why did Ms. Lin bring someone like her here?
天哪，为什么林小姐 带她这样的人来这儿？
Let's wait and see.
让我们等着看。
There must be a reason why he called her.
他给她打电话一定是有原因的。
Do your parents need help?
你的父母需要帮助吗？
Come?
来？
Take one of mine as an example.
拿我的一张来说吧。
No, I want someone official…
不，我想要一个正式的人……
listen.
听。
Maeng, you go back and deal with the partner agencies.
Maeng，你回去 和合作伙伴机构打交道吧。
Kim and Lee, you are mutual customers of Ryu.
Kim 和Lee， 你们是Ryu 的共同客户。
then…
当时…
Ryu, the first team is short-handed. You can help them.
Ryu，第一队人手不足。 你可以去帮助他们。
OK?
好的？
Well, in short,
嗯，简而言之，
I would be happy to have it.
我会很高兴拥有它。
They will have a free desk. You are moving today.
他们将有一张免费办公桌。 你今天要搬家了。
OK
好的。
sorry sir. song.
对不起，先生。歌曲。
I think this is too sudden...
我觉得这太突然了...
correct. I hope.
正确的。我希望。
Voiceover: Organizational Assessment
画外音：组织评估
Did you know we are in the VO period?
你知道我们正处于VO时期吗？
But we don’t have much to do with that. It’s the managers who do it…
但我们与此没有太多关系。 是经理们做的……
Not that.
不是那个。
Use your brain.
动动脑子。
What does a team leader do?
团队领导做什么？
-They evaluate performance. -Yes.
-他们评估绩效。 -是的。
Who is running for promotion?
谁在竞选晋升？
I'm running for deputy director.
我正在竞选 副主任。
Hugil e Jaemin is a manager.
Hugil e Jaemin 是一名经理。
Is there anyone else besides Seung Hee?
除了胜熙之外还有其他人吗？
Sir, I am running for Assistant Manager.
先生，我正在竞选 助理经理。
All four? OMG.
全部四个？我的天啊。
and…
和…
Damn, this is not good.
该死，这可不好。
You know I can only give one of them an A, right?
你知道我只能给其中一个人打 A，对吧？
So shameful.
太丢脸了。
I want to give it to those who are running
我想把它送给那些正在竞选的人
But you are all here.
但你们都在这里。
You have to take care of yourself.
你必须自己照顾自己。
you are right?
你说的是？
there is nothing. should go.
没有什么。应该去。
Team 1 needs help.
第 1 队需要帮助。
A PR office is a family.
公关办公室是一个家庭。
We should support each other.
我们应该互相支持。
correct.
正确的。
It became a simple matter.
这变成了一件简单的事情。
Assistant Ji Dachun
吉大春助理
Ointment, yes. Give it to Dachun
药膏，是的。给大春吧
It's a pleasure to work with you.
很高兴与您合作。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
Come?
来？
Aren't you planning on moving?
你不打算搬家吗？
You're only here for a few days, right?
你只待几天，对吗？
I have no idea…
我不知道…
We need someone who really works for our team.
我们需要一个 真正为我们的团队工作的人。
They want me to go crazy.
他们想让我发疯。
Do you smoke?
你抽烟吗？
-No. -Are you really not smoking?
-不。 -你真的不抽烟吗？
Or don't you want to smoke with me?
或者你不想和我一起抽烟吗？
No, I really don't smoke.
不，我真的不抽烟。
I quit.
我不干了。
Public Relations Team 1 Planning/Social Contribution
公关团队 1 策划/社会贡献
Pretty scary, right?
很可怕，对吧？
Public Relations Team 1 Planning/Social Contribution
公关团队 1 策划/社会贡献
CELLTICS ACTIVITIES COMPREHENSIVE PLAN
CELLTICS 活动 综合计划
Let's start.
让我们开始。
The first activity of the event: pop-up store
活动首个活动： 快闪店
They will open tomorrow near the university campus.
他们将于明天 在大学校园附近开业。
The second event is a shared office a week later.
第二次活动是 一周后的共享办公室。
OK
好的。
What about online advertising?
在线广告呢？
We sent her a new storyboard with changes.
我们向她发送了经过更改的新故事板。
We will start with your approval.
我们将在您批准后开始。
Park assistant?
公园助理？
Yes.
是的。
You know that, right?
你知道，对吧？
Ms. Park Yoon-joo will be in charge of Celltics.
朴允珠小姐 将负责Celltics。
I want to talk about fonts
我想谈谈字体
and color.
和颜色。
We've discussed this many times.
我们已经讨论过很多次了。
Jihyo said that this would be the last time.
志效说过， 这将是最后一次。
Oh sorry. I think you've decided everything.
哦对不起。 我想你已经决定了一切。
No, please tell us what you think.
不，请告诉我们您的想法。
OK
好的。
Since there is a new person in the project, why don't we have dinner together?
既然项目里来了一个新人，我们为什么不一起吃晚饭呢？
tonight?
今天晚上？
Yes, we can leave after the meeting.
是的，我们可以在会议结束后离开。
It's easier than setting another date.
这比设定另一个日期更容易。
Yes, it's okay.
是的，没关系。
Well, of course.
好吧，当然。
Park Assistant.
公园助理。
-Yes, Mrs. Ji. -Why did you apologize to them?
-是的，季太太。 -你为什么向他们道歉？
You have a responsibility. Please check if necessary.
你有责任。 如果有必要的话请检查一下。
There's nothing to apologize for, so no need to apologize.
没什么可道歉的， 所以不用道歉。
If you have an attitude of submission,
如果你有顺服的态度，
It will be harder to give orders in the future.
以后下命令就更难了。
OK
好的。
You no longer work for an agency.
您不再在代理机构工作。
Remember where you stand before you say or do something.
在说或做某事之前记住你的立场。
Okay, I know.
好的我知道了。
let's go.
我们走吧。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Why are you still working?
你为什么还在工作？
It's still early.
现在还早。
I'm hungry. let's go.
我饿了。我们走吧。
Shouldn't we meet at the restaurant?
我们不是应该在餐厅见面吗？
Come on, let's go!
来吧，我们走吧！
I know Jung called you.
我知道荣格打电话给你。
what did he say?
他说什么？
He blamed me for my bad work.
他因为我工作不好而责备我。
What?
什么？
Has the great Goo Yi Jung been scolded?
伟大的具宜正被骂了吗？
Fortunately he didn't let me put my hands in the air.
还好他没有让我 双手举在空中。
But I bet he's shy.
但我敢打赌他很腼腆。
Kim is a jerk, right?
金是个混蛋吧？
A real asshole.
一个真正的混蛋。
Anyway,
反正，
Is a public apology really necessary ?
真的有必要 公开道歉吗？
Yes.
是的。
There are not only users.
不仅有用户。
We must treat our employees as customers
我们必须将员工视为 客户
And satisfy them too.
并也满足他们。
Times have changed.
时代变了。
Every employee is a media channel
每一位员工 都是一个媒体渠道
Their posts can become newspaper articles.
他们的帖子 可以成为报纸文章。
Their negative comments about the company resulted in bad publicity
他们对公司的负面评价 导致了不良宣传
This could cause the share price to fall
这可能会导致 股价下跌
Miss.
女士。
I see.
我明白。
OK
好的。
Oh my God, you scare me.
天哪，你吓到我了。
What types of images work best?
什么类型的图像效果最好？
I've thought about this.
我想过这个问题。
How about an AD who is a good communicator?
善于沟通的AD怎么样？
AD that communicates well with the MZ generation.
与MZ世代沟通良好的AD 。
That's a good idea,
这个主意不错，
But to become one of them, she must communicate with them.
但要成为他们中的一员， 她就必须与他们沟通。
Can we be less formal outside of work?
工作之外我们可以不那么正式吗？
It's more difficult for me.
对我来说更困难。
Well, whatever you think.
好吧，随你怎么想。
first,
首先，
In order to communicate well with them, you have to listen to them.
为了与他们进行良好的沟通， 你必须倾听他们的意见。
What’s so hard about listening?
倾听有什么难的？
We have a digital PR team, right?
我们有数字公关团队，对吧？
I will find someone to help me.
我会找人来帮助我。
The problem is solved. It's easy.
问题解决了。这很容易。
Not if they don't talk.
如果他们不说话就不会。
Do you trust your employees to open up to you?
你相信你的员工 能够向你敞开心扉吗？
This is where the problem lies.
这就是问题所在。
As far as I know, Generation MZ is outspoken,
据我所知， MZ一代是直言不讳的，
This will make you angry.
这会让你生气。
Hanyu Fashion CEO Kang said.
汉宇时尚CEO康表示。
They don't do this to just anyone.
他们不只对任何人这样做。
-So, should I do it or not? -I say you have to do it right.
-那么，我做还是不做？ -我说你必须做对。
That's why I brought you here.
这就是我带你来这里的原因。
rely on you.
靠你了。
my God.
我的上帝。
Things were different for the third team.
第三队的情况有所不同。
You eat this.
你吃这个。
This is date food, not a business dinner.
这是约会的食物， 而不是商务晚餐。
Sorry, why are you here?
抱歉，你到底为什么来这里？
Him, because before he took charge.
他，因为在他负责之前。
And me, because I'm a new manager and a new manager at a partner agency.
还有我，因为我是新任经理， 也是合作伙伴机构的新经理。
AD Seo, you don’t mind?
AD Seo，你不介意吧？
I really love her.
我真的很爱她。
Luo arrived?
罗到？
OK I see.
好的。我明白。
As the gatekeeper, I propose a toast.
作为看门人，我提议干杯。
- Raise your glasses. -it's no use.
- 举起你的眼镜。 -这是没有用的。
-let's go. -Seriously, cheers?
-我们走吧。 -说真的，干杯吗？
Raise your glasses. strength.
举起你的眼镜。力量。
I will make a beautiful one.
我会做一个漂亮的。
OK I wish Celltics great success.
好的。 祝 Celltics 取得巨大成功。
salute!
礼炮！
-We are a good team. -healthy.
-我们是一支优秀的团队。 -健康。
cheers.
干杯。
-Thanks.
-谢谢。
I look forward to working with you.
我期待着与您合作。
Me too.
我也是。
For the record, this isn't the meal we're talking about.
根据记录，这不算 是我们谈论的那顿饭。
Come?
来？
remember? I'd like to treat you to something to eat.
回忆？我想请你吃点东西。
We're doing it now, aren't we?
我们现在就在做，不是吗？
Yes, but with other people.
是的，但是和其他人一起。
I did not mean that. I mean just the two of us.
我不是那个意思。 我的意思是只有我们两个人。
Just the two of us?
只有我们俩？
So this is a date, right?
所以这是一次约会，对吧？
excuse me. I'm kidding.
打扰一下。我在开玩笑。
OK
好的。
Your whole body turned red.
你整个人都红了。
I get drunk very easily.
我很容易喝醉酒。
It's a little hot in here, isn't it?
这里有点热，不是吗？
Is it yummy?
好不好吃？
Do you like it?
你喜欢它？
Yes.
是的。
Next time we will organize a formal dinner.
下次我们将组织 正式晚宴。
I think.
我想。
Hello sir. song.
先生你好。歌曲。
OK
好的。
I'm waiting.
我在等待。
Until we meet again.
直到我们再次见面。
I don't need wine anymore.
我不再需要酒了。
It's new.
它是新的。
Drinks are paid for by the company.
酒费由公司支付。
gentlemen. Song went out to drink.
先生。宋出去喝酒了。
so?
所以？
He needs a ride.
他需要搭车。
I provided.
我提供了。
This shows how difficult it is to make a living.
由此可见 谋生有多么困难。
You'll see it soon.
你很快就会看到它。
people.
人们。
Did you know that Jaemin is helping Team 1 now?
你知道在民现在帮助Team 1吗？
He will no longer write press releases.
他将不再撰写新闻稿。
Wait, why?
等等，为什么？
No one writes press releases better than him.
没有人比他更擅长撰写新闻稿。
Why are you doing this to me?
你为什么这样对我？
Talk to Mr. Song.
和先生谈谈吧 歌曲。
your thoughts.
你的想法。
Because Jaemin defended Park Yoon Jo in "Blahbla", right?
因为渽民 在《Blahbla》中为朴允祖辩护，对吧？
seriously. This speaks volumes about his character.
严重地。这充分说明 了他的个性。
Did you save me?
你救了我吗？
Why don't you apologize to him?
你为什么不向他道歉？
everything is fine.
一切安好。
Work is less stressful.
工作压力较小。
Honestly, it's better this way.
老实说，这样更好。
What did you do to protect her ?
为了保护她，你到底做了什么 ？
It is nothing special.
没什么特别的。
And it has nothing to do with her.
而且这与她无关。
Are you sure you're okay?
你确定你没事吗？
correct.
正确的。
Why?
为什么？
Come on, Team 1 isn't that bad.
得了吧，1队没那么糟糕。
What are you doing there?
你在那做什么？
Organizing a dinner party?
组织晚宴？
Yes.
是的。
Team leaders and managers
团队领导者和管理者
The Strategic Management Department will have dinner together this Friday.
战略管理部 将于本周五共进晚餐。
-Should I organize it? -Yes.
-我应该组织一下吗？ -是的。
Gi assistant is busy dealing with university testers. correct?
Gi助理正忙着 和大学测试人员打交道。正确的？
Yes, gosh…
是的，天哪……
I need you to do it.
我需要你去做。
Yes, there will be 15 to 20 people.
是的，会有 15 到 20 人。
Yes.
是的。
drinks.
饮料。
Drinks...please wait.
饮料……请稍等。
Assistant Ji.
吉助理。
What do executives drink?
高管喝什么？
If it's a Korean restaurant, soju with ice and tonic.
如果是韩国餐厅， 烧酒加冰和补品。
If it is a Western restaurant, whiskey or expensive wine.
如果是西餐厅， 威士忌或者名贵的酒。
I see.
我明白。
soon?
很快？
To drink, soju is served with ice and tonic water.
饮用时，烧酒加冰和汤力水。
Yes, please. Until we meet again.
是的，请。直到我们再次见面。
excuse me.
打扰一下。
Should I go to dinner too?
我也要去吃晚饭吗？
Who else would stand at the counter?
还有谁会站在柜台前
Escort them to the table?
护送他们到餐桌上？
Why are you acting ignorant?
你为何表现得无知？
Do you eat with reporters?
你和记者一起吃饭吗？
I wouldn't eat there...
我不会在那里吃饭...
I'm currently busy having students test the product,
我目前正忙着让学生 测试产品，
Make sure everything goes smoothly.
确保一切顺利。
You are a smart person. I believe you will succeed.
你是个聪明人。 我相信你会成功的。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Is there a coffee break in the sales department ?
业务部 有茶歇吗？
It's too late now.
现在已经晚了。
No, it's not too late.
不，现在还不算晚。
We are on time.
我们准时。
This is not true.
这不是真的。
You are late.
你晚了。
let's go.
我们走吧。
I invited them to tea.
我请他们喝茶。
Reason for delay.
延迟的原因。
So, have you ever thought about it?
那么，你有想过吗？
We recommend Jung Soo Hwan
我们推荐郑秀焕
Take on the role of Strategy Director.
担任战略总监一职。
He can't come today because he is on a business trip abroad.
他今天不能来， 因为他在国外出差。
“Noi” ambition?
“Noi”志？
Come?
来？
Are we officially on the same side?
我们正式站在一边了吗？
AD Lin.
AD 林。
Let's start the meeting.
我们开始会议吧。
Now we have to go.
现在我们得走了。
AD Lin.
AD 林。
Marketing Director Jung Soo-hwan.
营销总监郑秀焕。
When I…
当我…
I start here, from the bottom,
我从这里开始，从底层开始，
Kim is my team manager
Kim 是我的团队经理
Jeong Suhwan serves as assistant manager.
郑秀焕 (Jeong Suhwan) 担任助理经理。
Everyone knows my dad is the CEO.
每个人都知道我父亲是首席执行官。
He created a new department for me.
他为我创建了一个新部门。
i still can't forget
我仍然无法忘记
They looked at me with evil eyes.
他们用恶毒的眼神看着我。
They looked down on me and laughed at me.
他们瞧不起我 ，嘲笑我。
They only see me as the CEO’s daughter,
他们只看到我是总裁的女儿，
Not my strong point.
不是我的优点。
I hated the education they received in front of me.
我讨厌他们在我面前所受的教育。
This is part of the past.
这是过去的一部分。
It matters now.
现在很重要。
Do you think they have changed?
你觉得他们变了吗？
I'm not talking about them.
我不是在谈论他们。
I'm talking about you. You are a different person.
我正在谈论你。你是一个不同的人。
I was serious.
我是认真的。
Anyway,
反正，
It can't be Zheng
不可能是郑
You know.
你知道的。
If he becomes director of strategy, they'll chop off my legs.
如果他成为战略总监， 他们就会砍掉我的腿。
i will really be
我真的会成为
Just a puppet.
只是一个傀儡。
All I have left is you, the helpless CCO.
我就只剩下你 这个无能为力的CCO了。
I should name you Director of Strategy, CSO.
我应该任命你为 战略总监，CSO。
Actually, no.
事实上，没有。
They approve you as CCO, but what about CSO?
他们批准你担任 CCO，但是 CSO 呢？
They would tear me to pieces.
他们会把我撕成碎片。
So I want to have dinner with the strategy department.
所以我想 和战略部门一起吃晚饭。
They're on my side. I should make my presence felt.
他们站在我这边。 我应该让人感觉到我的存在。
Who will manage my social activities?
谁来管理我的社交活动？
Park Yoonjo, assistant manager of the PR 3 team.
PR 3 团队的助理经理 Park Yoonjo 。
-Blabula's girlfriend? -You know who he is.
-布拉布拉的女朋友？ -你知道他是谁。
AD who is good at communication. view?
善于沟通的AD。看法？
correct.
正确的。
Talk to the designer and let me know.
与设计师交谈并让我知道。
of course.
当然是的。
Is this store open at noon?
这家店中午开门吧？
Of course I'll be there.
当然，我会在那里。
AD SEO will come to get you.
AD SEO 会来接你。
it's no use. We see them.
这是没有用的。我们看到他们了。
he insisted. See you later.
他坚持说。我们稍后再见。
I'll pick you up in 30 minutes
30分钟后我来接你
Go to the store on the left side of the intersection.
到路口左边的商店。
Jihyo, do you want to come?
智孝，你想来吗？
Celltics’ offline event begins today.
Celltics 的线下活动今天开始。
Didn't you hear what Team Leader Ji said to me?
你没听到 季组长跟我说的话吗？
I finally have my own client
我终于有自己的客户了
I am very busy.
我很忙。
What product is it?
它是什么产品？
Protein powder.
蛋白粉。
protein?
蛋白质？
I know something.
我知道一些事情。
Yes, I'm sure that's the case.
是的，我确信情况就是如此。
dairy cow.
奶牛。
-greeting. -Yes, bye.
-问候。 -是的，再见。
-I'll accompany you. -Thanks.
-我陪你。 -谢谢。
Yunzhu, I brought you coffee. and behind.
允珠，我给你带了咖啡。和后面。
Are they all for me?
他们都是为了我吗？
I didn't know you liked it.
我不知道你喜欢它。
But there are many.
但有很多。
That's a bit much, AD Seo.
这有点多了，AD Seo。
Vero?
维罗？
I mean, I think it's a little too much.
我的意思是，我也觉得 有点过分了。
I have no preference for coffee.
我对咖啡没有偏好。
Drink iced coffee when it’s hot, drink latte when you’re hungry
天热的时候喝冰咖啡， 饿的时候喝拿铁
Sweet when I need sugar.
当我需要糖时又甜。
Then, you can drink them all.
然后，你就可以把它们全部喝掉了。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
Yes!
是的！
Hi everyone, before I start I will explain the rules.
大家好，在开始之前我会解释一下规则。
Hello, try here.
你好，来这里试试。
here it is.
这里是。
Win a bottle.
赢得一瓶。
-welcome. -greeting.
-欢迎。 -问候。
Congratulations!
恭喜！
Thanks.
谢谢。
Shall we go to the next one?
我们去下一个吗？
correct.
正确的。
Yin Qiao, please forgive me.
尹乔，请原谅一下。
soon?
很快？
OK I see.
好的。我明白。
Thanks.
谢谢。
excuse me,
打扰一下，
But I have to have a conference call with Tony from Traders.
但我必须 与 Traders 的托尼进行电话会议。
can I see?
我可以看吗？
affim. You are the customer.
肯定。你是客户。
Hi Tony. How is it going?
嗨，托尼。最近好吗？
-Hello. Excellent. you? -Excellent.
-你好。出色地。你？ -出色地。
This is my colleague, Yoonjo.
这是我的同事，Yoonjo。
Hi, nice to meet you.
你好，很高兴见到你。
goodbye.
再见。
So, what about media planning?
那么，媒体计划呢？
As our current media plan focuses more on online platforms,
由于我们目前的媒体计划 更多地关注网络平台，
We can consider shifting our focus to mobile devices.
我们可以考虑 将注意力转移到移动设备上。
Research shows that the average Korean
研究表明 ，韩国人平均
More than 50% of purchases are made via mobile phones.
超过 50% 的购物行为是 通过手机进行的。
Based on this unique panorama,
基于这独特的全景，
I believe
我相信
Shift focus to mobile platforms
将重点 转向移动平台
By diversifying our inventory, we can expect better results.
通过库存多元化， 我们可以期待更好的结果。
We agree with you about changing the media plan.
我们同意您 更改媒体计划的意见。
We will investigate this further as well as the inventory.
我们将进一步调查这一点 以及库存。
Sorry, we have to go now. But we’ll get to that later.
抱歉，我们现在得走了。 但我们稍后再讨论。
affim. We'll talk soon.
肯定。我们很快就会谈。
Thanks. Until we meet again.
谢谢。直到我们再次见面。
Thank you, good bye.
谢谢你再见。
-Hello. - Until we meet again.
-你好。 -直到我们再次见面。
my God.
我的上帝。
Bravo, AD Seo.
太棒了，AD Seo。
-You can do absolutely anything, right? -Thanks.
-你绝对可以做任何事情，对吧？ -谢谢。
With Celltics, your skin will never be dry again !
使用 Celltics，您的皮肤将不再干燥 ！
Do you want to spin the wheel?
你想转动轮子吗？
Spin the wheel and win prizes.
旋转轮盘并赢得奖品。
one two three.
一二三。
-excellent!
-极好的！
This is great.
这真好。
This is something you've always done, right?
这是你一直在做的事情，对吧？
View events offline,
离线查看活动，
Hold meetings with your foreign partners
与您的外国合作伙伴举行会议
Then find customers yourself.
然后自己去找客户。
I already told you, right?
我已经告诉过你了，对吧？
Like you, I put a lot of effort into my work.
我和你一样，为工作投入了很多精力。
It's not easy for me to be satisfied with myself.
我不容易 对自己感到满意。
I also want to show others my worth.
我也想向别人展示 我的价值。
But you told me not to do that.
但你告诉我不要那样做。
I know.
我知道。
But it's hard.
但这很难。
Well, I admire that, but for your employees
好吧，我对此很钦佩， 但对你的员工来说
You may not like it.
你可能不喜欢它。
If the boss tries too hard, they will feel obligated to do so.
如果老板太努力， 他们就会觉得有义务这样做。
it is true.
是真的。
I never pick up customers. I'm only doing this for you.
我从不去接顾客。 我只是为了你才这么做的。
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
Because I like that.
因为我喜欢这样。
It's been a while since I attended an event like this.
我已经有一段时间 没有参加这样的活动了。
-No, again. -OMG.
-不，再一次。 -我的天啊。
- Like this. ——That must be the case.
-像这样做。 ——一定是这样。
-No, it's not. You are all wrong. - Like this.
-不，不是的。你全都错了。 -像这样做。
-No. - Rotate your wrist twice.
-不。 - 旋转手腕两次。
-Before doing this? -Let's try again.
-在这样做之前？ -让我们再试一次。
If it doesn't work, we change.
如果不起作用，我们就改变。
-OK. -hurry up. Hey, get ready.
-好的。 -快点。嘿，准备好了。
It's going too fast.
进展太快了。
Forza.
极限竞速。
I'm fine! continue!
我没事！继续！
-Hey, did you see that? -Very good.
-嘿，你看到了吗？ -太好了。
class president!
课代表！
Hey, rep.
嘿，代表。
What…
什么…
-what is that? -what is what?
-那是什么？ -什么是什么？
I want to say...
我想说……
You also have good grades.
你也有很好的成绩。
This isn't fair. Why do you dance so well?
这不公平。为什么你跳舞跳得好？
Because I learned.
因为我学会了。
I take dance classes.
我上舞蹈课。
-Why? -as.
-为什么？ -作为。
Anti-stress.
抗压力。
I hate you.
我恨你。
Hey, rep.
嘿，代表。
you can…
你可以…
Can you teach me the previous steps?
可以教我之前的步骤吗？
But if you hate me.
但如果你讨厌我。
I hate you because you are strong.
我恨你，因为你很强。
So, come on.
所以，来吧。
Taught me.
教我。
Yes?
是的？
Utopia
乌托邦
it's a pity.
真可惜。
OK
好的。
Hey, Yoon-kyo can't come.
嘿，允乔不能来。
cabbage.
卷心菜。
Hey, your hands are shaking.
嘿，你的手在颤抖。
That idiot. Qi Dachun, this bastard...
那个白痴。奇大春这个混蛋……
What does he have, some kind of inferiority complex?
他有什么，某种 自卑感？
What?
什么？
How do you understand this?
你是怎么理解这一点的？
Judging from the things you said.
从你说的这些事情来看。
Always an assistant manager, never promoted.
一直是助理经理， 从来没有升职。
He switched from sales to PR less than a year ago .
不到一年前， 他就从销售转向公关。
You're not friends and you don't know.
你们不是朋友而且你不知道
Who is grumpy and intolerant.
谁脾气暴躁、不宽容。
And he hated those who came out of the draft.
而且他讨厌那些从选拔中出来的人。
Oh my gosh, yeah.
天哪，恩。
Your technology has improved.
你的技术进步了。
Come on, you can't call it a skill.
得了吧，你不能称之为技能。
I deal with a lot of people here.
我在这里和很多人打交道。
They were happy when I remembered details about them.
当我记得有关他们的细节时，他们很高兴。
This is a skill. business skills.
这是一项技能。业务技能。
how about you? You really don't?
那你呢？你真的没有吗？
-That? - Feeling of inferiority.
-那？ -自卑感。
Everyone feels inferior about something .
每个人都会因为某些事情而感到自卑 。
Jaemin.
宰民。
Nice to meet you.
见到你很高兴。
Hey, what are you doing here?
嘿，你在这里做什么？
This is a bar. I'm obviously here for a drink.
这是一家酒吧。我显然是来喝酒的。
-Well, I'm back. -Hello.
-恩，我回来了。 -你好。
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
I take the usual approach.
我采取平常的方式。
Understood.
明白了。
"usually?"
“通常？”
Now I come here often.
现在我经常来这里。
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
Inferiority complex?
自卑感？
Do you know what it is?
你知道它是什么吗？
Why does everyone say this?
为什么大家都这么说呢？
I would be flattered if you thought I was so perfect .
如果你认为我如此完美， 我将感到受宠若惊。
but I am not.
但我不是。
Even now I still feel very pitiful
到现在我还是觉得很可怜
and deficiencies.
和不足。
I feel the same way.
我也有这样的感觉。
And you? What makes you feel inferior?
你呢？是什么让你感到自卑？
I don't think there is anything.
我不认为有什么。
I lack talent.
我缺乏才华。
That's a big inferiority complex, isn't it?
这是一个很大的自卑感，不是吗？
Is it you, huh?
是你吗，恩？
I worry about the rent every month
我每个月都为房租发愁
I thought to myself:
我心里想：
"What am I doing?"
“我在做什么？”
“What am I selling here, drinks or my soul?”
“我在这里卖什么， 饮料还是我的灵魂？”
Poor, right?
可怜吧？
How about an expensive cocktail?
来一杯昂贵的鸡尾酒怎么样？
Your friend?
你的朋友？
-Yes, of course.
-是的，当然了。
You always drink expensive stuff.
你总是喝昂贵的东西。
Next month brings some expensive rent.
下个月带来一些 昂贵的租金。
One million and eight.
一百万零八。
-Hey, I gotta go. -Hey, where are you going?
-嘿，我得走了。 -嘿，你要去哪里？
-let it be! -Hey!
-随它去！ -嘿！
Why are you working so hard?
你这么辛苦是为了什么？
Submit budget increase report.
提交预算增加报告。
This is Kat's job.
这是吉的工作。
I knew it.
我就知道。
He gave it to you, didn't he?
他给了你，不是吗？
Yes, why?
是的，为什么？
Well, you'll see soon enough.
好吧，你很快就会看到。
Obviously,
显然，
Kim wants Jeong to serve as marketing director,
Kim 希望 Jeong 担任营销总监，
is the new chief security officer.
是新任首席安全官。
So the captains panicked.
于是，队长们都慌了。
Why?
为什么？
Why? In your opinion?
为什么？依你的意见？
Zheng Xiuhuan is under the protection of her husband. gold.
郑秀焕在先生的庇护下。金.
If he becomes chief strategy officer, what do you think that means?
如果他成为首席战略官， 您认为这意味着什么？
Who wants to get rid of all AD Lim’s followers ?
谁想除掉 AD Lim 的所有追随者
in strategic management.
在战略管理中。
Hey, think about it.
嘿，想想吧。
Would you let the CCO go when no one knew what it was for?
当没人知道CCO 的用途时，您会放过它吗？
What went wrong with the CCO?
CCO 出了什么问题？
What's the point if no one's here
如果没人在这里还有什么意义
sa want me to write "communication"?
sa来我写“沟通”吗？
And then it comes from abroad.
然后它来自国外。
She was like an intruder.
她就像一个入侵者。
You don't even know how to spell it.
你甚至不知道如何拼写它。
Why do such experienced people come to work here?
这么有经验的人为什么 来这里工作？
To me, he had no idea what he was getting into.
对我来说，他不知道 自己正在陷入什么境地。
I don't know either.
我也不知道。
of course not.
当然不是。
You are a simple assistant manager.
你是一个简单的助理经理。
correct.
正确的。
Where are they going to have dinner tonight?
今晚他们去哪里吃晚饭？
Algoladen.
阿尔戈拉登。
At that Korean restaurant?
在那家韩国餐厅？
It has a great menu. correct.
它有一个很棒的菜单。正确的。
race,
赛，
That place is a bit old. They must sit on the floor.
那个地方有点旧了。 他们必须坐在地板上。
What will Ms. Gu and Ms. Lin wear?
古女士和林女士会穿什么？
Will wearing a skirt look uncomfortable?
穿裙子会不会看起来不舒服？
where are you going? Where are you two going?
你要去哪里？你们两个要去哪里？
curse.
诅咒。
Look at the time. They will go out to meet with reporters.
看看时间。 他们将出去会见记者。
Why only them?
为什么只有他们？
Kim Hugill, that bastard.
金休吉尔，那个混蛋。
-In my opinion, Seunghee will get an A. -Why?
-在我看来，Seunghee 会得到 A。 -为什么？
She is the smartest of the three of you.
她是你们三个中最聪明的一个。
CELLTICS pop-up store survey
CELLTICS快闪店问卷调查
How do you rate skin care products? (from 0 to 100)
您如何评价护肤品？（从 0 到 100）
11% are male, 5% have no opinion, and 84% are female.
男性 11%， 无意见 5%，女性 84%
Skin type, problem
皮肤类型、问题
Twenty years old: 39, thirty years old: 43
二十岁：39，三十岁：43
Forty years old: 71 Fifty years old: 74 Sixty years old and above: 63
四十岁：71 五十岁：74 六十岁及以上：63
Gao Litong
高丽童
Here they come.
他们来了。
Hello madam.
女士你好。
Lu, check it out...
鲁，检查一下……
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
Gao Litong
高丽童
-This way. -Thanks.
-这边走。 -谢谢。
Hello madam.
女士你好。
-Come in quickly. -OK.
-快点进去吧。 -好的。
Sigra Ji.
西格拉·吉.
-here. -Thanks.
-这里。 -谢谢。
This is me.
这就是我。
Tonight you'll be sitting on the floor,
今晚你将坐在地板上，
You may find the skirt uncomfortable.
你可能会觉得裙子不舒服。
Guijeong
具宜正
Thanks.
谢谢。
This way.
这边走。
Fill all the cups.
把所有的杯子都装满。
very good.
非常好。
Sigla Gu.
西格拉·古。
Thanks.
谢谢。
First I want to express all my love
首先我想表达 我全部的爱
Author: Lin Zhixian AD.
作者：林智贤 AD。
Now let us hear his toast.
现在让我们听听他的祝酒词。
I always make the same toast.
我总是做同样的吐司。
which one?
哪一个？
- Leeteuk!
- 利特！
-L! -Work!
-L！ -工作！
-and! -Excellent!
-和！ -出色的！
-And enthusiasm!
-还有热情！
-T! -They will turn you into a leader
-T！ -他们会把你变成领导者
——Your generation! -healthy!
——你们这一代人！ -健康！
Let's start eating, shall we?
我们开始吃饭吧，好吗？
Yes.
是的。
AD Lin.
AD 林。
Every time I hear his toast, I feel like I'm getting an electric shock
每次听到他的祝酒词 我都像触电一样
Run through my body.
跑过我的身体。
-Really? -Yes.
-真的吗？ -是的。
That toast…
那个吐司……
Did you learn it from Kim Yeon Soo?
是跟金妍秀学的吧？
He taught her when she was a newbie.
当她还是个新人的时候，他就教过她。
I think I'll leave now.
我想我现在就离开。
Then maybe I should...
那么也许我应该……
No.
不。
Your subtraction.
你的减法。
This dinner is to welcome you. Stay.
这顿晚宴 是为了欢迎您。停留。
nobody
没有人
He had to chase me to stop me.
他必须追我才能阻止我。
-Ms. Gu, can you? -affim.
-古女士，可以吗？ -肯定。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I am Song Suntae from the Public Relations Team 2.
我是公关2组的宋善太。
Yes, nice to meet you.
是的，很高兴见到你。
She focuses on ASG,
她专注于 ASG，
This is of interest to every society today.
这是 当今每个社会都感兴趣的。
correct.
正确的。
So I have some questions for you.
所以我有一些问题想问你。
She is a public information officer. How did you change careers?
她是一名新闻官员。 你是如何改变职业的？
Is it easier to do this in other countries?
在其他国家这样做更容易吗？
not completely…
不完全是…
I am also very curious.
我也很好奇。
Frankly, the whole concept of ASG is impractical for Korean businesses.
坦率地说，ASG的整个概念 对于韩国企业来说是不切实际的。
We do this because foreign companies
我们这样做是因为外国公司
They impose it on us.
他们把它强加给我们。
Consumers and markets are changing,
消费者和市场 正在发生变化，
It also depends on the company.
这也取决于公司。
This is the base.
这是基地。
question?
问题？
Is the situation different in South Korea?
韩国的情况有什么不同吗？
Well, not exactly.
嗯，不完全是。
She looks like a real pro.
她看起来像个真正的专家。
Well
嘛
How did you become an ASG expert?
您是如何 成为 ASG 专家的？
The core of ASG is communication.
ASG的核心是沟通。
The same goes for PR, right?
PR也是如此，对吧？
correct.
正确的。
I think this is a more than adequate answer.
我认为这是一个 绰绰有余的答案。
Well, I might as well suggest
好吧，我不妨建议
The Office of Public Relations is responsible for ASG's practices.
公关办公室负责 ASG 的做法。
Every company's situation is different.
每个公司的情况都不同。
Some set up new departments,
有的设立新部门，
Others let them do strategic planning.
其他人则让他们 进行战略规划。
will
将会
It will definitely be more efficient to work with a PR expert.
与公关专家合作肯定会更有效率。
"PR expert."
“公关专家。”
It all looks very beautiful to me
这一切在我看来都非常美丽
She is definitely an expert.
她绝对是一位专家。
But why do PR departments need experts?
但为什么公关部门 需要专家呢？
Is there a PR department that doesn’t have experts?
有没有没有专家的公关部门？
Is La Seyong that kind of place?
La Seyong是那样的地方吗？
is that so?
是这样吗？
No.
不。
Seyong is more than just a place.
塞勇不仅仅是一个地方。
No, of course not.
不，当然不。
excuse me. I need to go to the toilet.
打扰一下。我需要去厕所。
Sigla Gu. Prego.
西格拉·古。普雷戈。
I want to learn a lot from her.
我想向她学习很多东西。
I'm glad you came to Seyong.
我很高兴您来到 Seyong。
I am Ji Eunjeong, leader of the PR 3 team.
我是 PR 3 组组长 Ji Eunjeong。
I can't wait to work with her.
我迫不及待地想和她一起工作。
I also look forward to working with you.
我也期待 与您合作。
Sigla Gu!
西格拉·古！
-hatred. - Mrs. Gu!
-恨。 -古太太！
Yes?
是的？
We're glad you're here!
我们很高兴您来到这里！
Thanks.
谢谢。
Choi Young-ho, leader of the Public Relations Team 1.
崔英浩，公关1组组长。
I see.
我明白。
Check,
查看，
I'm so glad she's here!
我很高兴她在这里！
correct.
正确的。
Now we have a great person like her in our PR office!
现在我们的公关办公室里有一个像她这样的好人！
It sounds like you drank too much.
听起来你喝得太多了。
Sigla Gu!
西格拉·古！
Hope it can improve the status of the public relations office!
希望能够提高 公关办公室的地位！
Not HR, strategic planning, or legal.
不是人力资源、 战略规划或法律。
PR office!
公关办公室！
That's it! healthy!
就是这样！健康！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Damn, I'm sorry.
该死，对不起。
-Hey, get up. -Hey.
-嘿，起来吧。 -嘿。
Hey. What?
嘿。什么？
Damn it, come on.
该死的，来吧。
Sun Tai, a cow.
孙泰，一头牛。
It's interesting. Yes.
这很有趣。是的。
- Come on, cheers. -OK.
-来吧，干杯。 -好的。
——One breath. We drink. -We drink.
——一口气。我们喝。 -我们喝。
I drank too much.
我喝太多了。
Until the last drop.
直到最后一滴。
for you. healthy.
给你。健康。
Sigla Gu.
西格拉·古。
Will he come to karaoke for round two?
他会来卡拉 OK 进行第二轮吗？
That's enough for today.
今天就够了。
What are you doing? Be there for her.
你在干什么？陪伴她。
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
you eat?
你吃？
No.
不。
Well done today.
今天干得好。
How about dinner?
晚餐怎么样？
used to be…
曾是…
Bad.
糟糕的。
I'm surprised you stayed.
我很惊讶你留下来了。
I thought if you didn't like it you would leave.
我以为如果你不喜欢的话你就会离开。
You have relented
你已经心软了
All right…
好吧…
You're just here to take a break.
你只是来这里休息一下。
Jaemin.
宰民。
So it is...
所以它是……
la Seyong.
la Seyong.
I can't help but hope.
我忍不住希望。
You solved the Blahbla problem
你解决了 Blahbla 问题
You are wonderful.
你太棒了。
I know Gu Yi Zheng.
我认识的具宜正。
Now that I know what kind of person you are,
既然我知道你是一个什么样的人，
I can't help but hope.
我忍不住希望。
Jung Soo-hwan
郑秀焕
Which of you is Park Yoon Joo?
你们谁是朴允珠？
Park Yoonjo of the PR 3 team. She wrote the report.
PR 3 团队的 Park Yoonjo。 她撰写了这份报告。
Where?
在哪里？
Subtitles: Alisa Copertini
字幕：艾丽莎·科佩尔蒂尼